J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - J. V. Messing to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Sept. 9 (Box 15)
  - C. W. Wende to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 Sept. 9 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Sept. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Sept. 26; Hall, James (Box 15)
  - E. T. Lincoln to Mrs. Lesley, 1875 Sept. 26 (Box 15)
  - James B. Thayer to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Oct. 5 (Box 15)
  - to Persifor Frazer, Jr., 1875 Oct. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to Persifor Frazer, 1875 Oct. 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 15)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Oct. 16; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Oct. 17; Thayer, J. B. (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Oct. 18; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Nov. 6; Thayer, J. B. (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Nov. 21-22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - C. E. Hall to J. P. Lesley, 1875 Nov. 24 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Nov. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Dec. 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - Alfred Langdon Elwyn to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1875 Dec. 11 (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Dec. 12; Thayer, J. B. (Box 15)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Dec. 14; Thayer, J. B. (Box 15)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1875 Dec. 17; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 15)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1875 Dec. 24; Guyot, A., (Arnold), 1807-1884 (Box 15)
  - Anna Jackson to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1875 Dec. 25 (Box 15)
  - to Miss Mary Lesley, 1875 Dec. 27; Henry, Joseph (Box 15)
  - Theodore Cuyler to Peter Lesley, 1876 Jan. 15 (Box 16)
  - to J. S. Newberry, 1876 Jan. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to J. S. Newberry, 1876 Jan. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Jan. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Harriet Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Jan. 28 (Box 16)
  - John Wilson and Son to Prof. Thayer, 1876 Jan. 31 (Box 16)
  - to Samuel Clements, 1876 Feb. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to A. Sherwood, 1876 Feb. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to Andrew Sherwood, 1876 Feb. 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to "My dear Tyndall, 1876 Feb. 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Feb. 27; Thayer, J. B. (Box 16)
  - Moncure D. Conway to Cousin Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1876? March 1 (Box 16)
  - to J. S. Newberry, 1876 March 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - Leo Lewquereux to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 March 5 (Box 16)
  - John Welsh to Mrs. Lesley, 1876 March 15 (Box 16)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 March 16 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 March 22; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 16)
  - to "My very dear Desor", 1876 March 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - F. A. P, Barnard to J. P. Lesley, 1876 March 25 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 March 31; Hall, James (Box 16)
  - F. A. P. Barnard to J. P. Lesley, 1876 April 8 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 April 15; Hall, James (Box 16)
  - Ch. W. Wendté to J. P. Lesley, 1876 April 17 (Box 16)
  - to H. F. Kenney, 1876 April 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1876 April 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Ellis Wark, 1876 April 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 May 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Mrs. Laura Gwinotte? to Miss Lesley, 1876? May 13 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1876 May 19; Barton, Susan R. (Box 16)
  - O. C. Marsh to J. P. Lesley, 1876 May 21 (Box 16)
  - Henry Whitney Bellows to Peter Lesley, 1876 May 27 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 May 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 June 3; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 June 9; Desor, Edouard (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 June 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Andrew Ramsay to J. P. Lesley, 1876 June 22 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 July 4; Desor, Edouard (Box 16)
  - George A. König to Mrs. Susan Inches Lesley, 1876 July 12 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 July 20; Desor, Edouard (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 July 25; Desor, Edouard (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Aug. 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Nellie Hale to Mary and Meg Lesley, 1876 Aug. 11 (Box 16)
  - Eliza O. White to "My dear girls" Mary and Margaret Lesley, 1876 Aug. 11 (Box 16)
  - Joseph Leidy to Mrs. Lesley, 1876 Aug. 17 (Box 16)
  - Mrs. Katherine E. F. Nicholls to Mary Lesley, 1876 Aug. 23 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Aug. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Sept. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Sept. 15; Thayer, J. B. (Box 16)
  - to William Lorenz, 1876 Sept. 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Stevenson, 1876 Sept. 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Sept. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Sept. 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Sept. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1876 Sept. 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Oct. 1; Thayer, J. B. (Box 16)
  - S. P. Hastings to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1876 Oct. 4 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Oct. 4; Thayer, J. B. (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Oct. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Ellen T. Emerson to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1876 Oct. 11 (Box 16)
  - J. E. Hilgard to J. P. Lesley, 1876 Oct. 13 (Box 16)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1876 Oct. 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1876 Oct. 23; Newberry, J. S., (John Strong), 1822-1892 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Oct. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1876 Oct. 28; Hale, Susan (Box 16)
  - C. L. B owman to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Nov. 6 (Box 16)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Nov. 12 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Nov. 17; Hall, James (Box 16)
  - Lucy Stone to Mrs. Lewis, 1876 Nov. 20 (Box 16)
  - to Joseph Henry, 1876 Nov. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - E. S. Turner to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Dec. 2 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Dec. 7; Desor, Edouard (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1876 Dec. 7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to Andrew Sherwood, 1876 Dec. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - Henry Whitney Bellows to Peter Lesley, 1876 Dec. 19 (Box 16)
  - Harriet Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1876 Dec. 22 (Box 16)
  - John G. Sieber to Leo Lesquereux, 1876 Dec. 26 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Jan. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Jan. 3 (Box 16)
  - Mrs. Elizabeth Gay to Mrs. Susie I. Lesley, 1877 Jan. 11 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Jan. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Jan. 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Moncure D. Conway to Cousin Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1877 Jan. 25 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Jan. 25; Swan, Martha L. (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Jan. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Ann Gilchrist to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1877 Feb. 3 (Box 16)
  - to Charles A. Ashburner, 1877 Feb. 6-7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - Charles Albert Ashburner to Leo Lesquereux, 1877 Feb. 9 (Box 16)
  - George William Childs to Mrs. J. P. Lesley, 1877 Feb. 26 (Box 16)
  - Joseph LeConte to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Feb. 26 (Box 16)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 March 8 (Box 16)
  - John Murray Forbes to J. P. Lesley, 1877 March 12 (Box 16)
  - J. D. Morrell to J. P. Lesley, 1877 March 12 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 March 12; Thompson, R. E. (Box 16)
  - to F. W. Forman, 1877 March 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - D. A. Goddard to J. B. Thayer, 1877 March 17 (Box 16)
  - to Mr. Shaler, 1877 March 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 March 24; Hall, James (Box 16)
  - to Stevenson, 1877 March 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 16)
  - to Mrs. Susan IlLesley, 1877 March 26; Frothingham, Octavius Brooks (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 March 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 16)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 April 1; Hall, James (Box 17)
  - to William M. Fontaine, 1877 April 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 April 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 April 8 (Box 17)
  - to William M. Fontaine, 1877 April 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - Charles D. Reed to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 April 10 (Box 17)
  - to Mr. Peter Lesley, 1877 April 17; Hale, Charles (Box 17)
  - Garland C. Broadhead to J. P. Lesley, 1874 April 18 (Box 17)
  - to Joseph Hartmann, 1877 April 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 April 28; Hall, James (Box 17)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 April 30 (Box 17)
  - to C. W. Rogers, 1877 May 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 May 26; Thayer, J. B. (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 May 31; Desor, Edouard (Box 17)
  - to J. C. White, 1877 June 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 June 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Mr. Ashburner, 1877 June 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 June 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 July 6; Thayer, J. B. (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 July 19; Thayer, J. B. (Box 17)
  - to Ira Winan, 1877 July 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - M. S. Mackintosh to Mrs. Lesley, 1877 July 23 (Box 17)
  - to Mr. Ashburner, 1877 July 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 July 24; Thayer, J. B. (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 July 25; Desor, Edouard (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Aug. 1; Henry, Joseph (Box 17)
  - to Stevenson, 1877 Aug. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - S. P. Hastings to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1877 Aug. 7 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Aug. 7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. G. Sieber, 1877 Aug. 7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - J. E. Hilgard to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Aug. 22 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Aug. 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Sept. 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - Maria A. Revere to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Sept. 7 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Sept. 7; Thayer, J. B. (Box 17)
  - Anna Richmond to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Sept. 9 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Sept. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Sept. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - Anna Richmond To Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Oct. 6 (Box 17)
  - Frederick Fraley to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Oct. 9 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Oct. 17; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Samuel H. Scudder, 1877 Oct. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - Delesse to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Oct. 27 (Box 17)
  - James Geikie to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Oct. 27 (Box 17)
  - to F. H. J. W.? Jones, 1877 Nov. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1877 Nov. 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Nov. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Nov. 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Nov. 23; LeConte, Joseph L. (Box 17)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1877 Nov. 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Nov. 24; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Nov. 25; Swan, Martha L. (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Nov. 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 1; LeConte, Joseph L. (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 3; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 17)
  - James D,. Dana to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 5 (Box 17)
  - to William Blazius, 1877 Dec. 3; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 17)
  - Eli K. Price to J. P. Lesley, 1877 Dec. 11 (Box 17)
  - to "My dear Hunt", 1877 Dec. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 17; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - Frederick Fraley to J.P. Lesley, 1877 Dec. 22 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1877 Dec. 26; Barton, Susan R. (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1877 Dec. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - C. J. Stillé to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Dec. 29 (Box 17)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1877 Dec. 30; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 17)
  - to J. J. Stevenson, 1878 Jan. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Jan. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - C. H. Hitchcock to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Jan. 24 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Jan. 26; Hall, James (Box 17)
  - Elizabeth Q. Guild to Susie I. Lesley, 1878 Jan. 27 (Box 17)
  - B. H. Bartol to Mrs. S. I. Lesley, 1878 Jan. 28 (Box 17)
  - to F. W. Forman, 1878 Feb. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to Susie I. Lesley, 1878 Feb. 10; Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909 (Box 17)
  - Isac Lea to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Feb. 10 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Feb. 12; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Warren Upham, 1878 Feb. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Feb. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1878 March 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J.Peter Lesley, 1878 March 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 7; Desor, Edouard (Box 17)
  - to E. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - C. J. Stillé to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 18 (Box 17)
  - C. J. Stille to Professor Lesley, 1878 March 18 (Box 17)
  - to Charles J. Stille, 1878 March 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - C. J. Stillé to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 19 (Box 17)
  - to Dr. Stille, 1878 March 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - C. J. Stillé to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 23 (Box 17)
  - to Frederick Fraley, 1878 March 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to Dr. Stillé, 1878 March 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 March 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 17)
  - Mr. L. Swan to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1878 March 31 (Box 17)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 April 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - E. T. Ware to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1878 April 6 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 April 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Edward Orton, 1878 April 12; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 April 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to L. E. Hicks, 1878? April 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - H. Höfer to J. P. Lesley, 1878 April 24 (Box 18)
  - H. Höfer to J. P. Lesley, 1878 April 24 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 April 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - B. Silliman to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 April 24 (Box 18)
  - to J. J. Stevenson, 1878 May 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 May 12; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 May 16; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 May 27; Cook, George H. (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 May 27; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 18)
  - to Prof. White, 1878 May 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to Charles Latimore, 1878 May 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - Joseph Lovering to Mrs. Lesley, 1878 May 30 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to J. D. Dana, 1878 June 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - Anna Richmond to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1878 June 14 (Box 18)
  - Telegram to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 19; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 22; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - S. M.Hall to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 24 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 June 25; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 18)
  - to Andrew Sherwood, 1878 June 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 June 27; Pepper, William (Box 18)
  - to J.Peter Lesley, 1878 June 29; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J.Peter Lesley, 1878 June 29; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Andrew Sherwood to James Hall, 1878 June (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 July 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 July 3; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Jed. Hotchkiss to J.P.Lesley, 1878 July 9 (Box 18)
  - Kate E. D. Nicholls to Mrs. Lesley, 1878 July 17 (Box 18)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 July 20 (Box 18)
  - Prof. Erdmann to J.Peter Lesley, 1878 July 23 (Box 18)
  - to J.Peter Lesley, 1878 July 26; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Aug. 5; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Aug. 15; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Aug. 16; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1878 Aug. 18; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Aug. 19; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Joseph May to Mrs. Lesley, 1878 Aug. 19 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Aug. 26; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Sept. 1; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Delesse to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Sept. 2 (Box 18)
  - E. L. Head?? to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley?, 1878? Sept. 2 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Sept. 3; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - E. L. Head to Mrs. Susan I.Lesley?, 1878 Sept. 3 (Box 18)
  - E. L.Head to Mrs. SusanI. Lesley, 1878 Sept. 4 (Box 18)
  - to P. W. Sheafer, 1878 Oct. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1878 Oct. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1878 Oct. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Oct. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1878 Oct. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to C.J. Stillé, 1878 Oct. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to Fairman Rogers, 1878 Oct. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Oct. 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - M. J. Burleigh to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1878 Oct. 20 (Box 18)
  - Elizabeth Q. Guild to Susie I. Lesley, 1878 Oct. 20 (Box 18)
  - Henry Whitney Bellows to John White Chadwick, 1878 Oct. 21 (Box 18)
  - Helen C. Jenks to Mrs. Lesley, 1878 Oct. 24 (Box 18)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1878 Oct. 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Oct. 27; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Elizabeth Gay to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1878 Oct. 31 (Box 18)
  - to Prof. Thompson, 1878 Nov. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - Mrs. Ann Gilchrist to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1878 Nov. 14 (Box 18)
  - to G. B. Stranch, 1878 Nov. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Nov. 19; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1878 Nov. 20; Thompson, R. E. (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Nov. 24; Desor, Edouard (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 1; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Dec. 2; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 4; Hall, James (Box 18)
  - Warren Upham to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 7 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - Adolphe Favre to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 15 (Box 18)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1878 Dec. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - Ashburner to E. B. Harden, 1878 Dec. 20 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Prof. Ennis, 1878 Dec. 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - Gertrude G. Biddle to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1878 Dec. 27 (Box 18)
  - Ch. Barrois to J. Peter Lesley, 1878 Dec. 28 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1878 Dec. 30; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Jan. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 Jan. 3; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Jan. 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1879 Jan. 4; Thompson, R. E. (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Jan. 11; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - to the Hon. Mr. Pattison, 1879 Jan. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1879 Jan. 16; Barton, Susan R. (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Jan. 18; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 Jan. 20; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 18)
  - to the Rev. Samuel Haughton, 1879 Jan. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 Jan. 31; Kerr, W. C. (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Feb. 3; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Feb. 6; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Pres. Hayes, 1879 Feb. 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Feb. 16; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 Feb. 17; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 18)
  - to Mr. Sheafer, 1879 Feb. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 Feb. 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - to Mr. Sheafer, 1879 Feb. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - to S. P. wolverton, 1879 Feb. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 18)
  - Jules Barrois to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1879 March 6 (Box 18)
  - Breton to Monsieur Barrois, 1879 March 8 (Box 18)
  - J. W. Powell to J. P. Lesley, 1879 March 8 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 March 9; Barois, Charles (Box 18)
  - B. Silliman to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 March 10 (Box 18)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 March 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 18)
  - William Channing Gannett to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1879 March 25 (Box 18)
  - Benjamin Smith Lyman to Mrs. Lyman, 1879 March 27 (Box 18)
  - Dr. Lauth to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 March 31 (Box 18)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1879 April 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 19)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 April 8; Barois, Charles (Box 19)
  - to James D. Dana, 1879 April 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 19)
  - Joseph LeConte to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 14 (Box 19)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 April 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 19)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 16; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 19)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 16; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 19)
  - Alfred R. C. Selwyn to F. Prince, Jr., 1879 April 17 (Box 19)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 April 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 19)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 19; Walling, H. F. (Box 19)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 April 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 19)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1879 April 24; Henderson, A. A. (Box 19)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1879 April 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 19)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 29; Hawes, George W. (Box 19)
  - M. E. Wadsworth to J. P. Lesley, 1879 April 29 (Box 19)
  - Alexander Agassiz to J. P. Lesley, 1879 May 2 (Box 19)